W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  - Department of Agriculture, 1916-1981, undated; 1
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2257, “Selecting and Using Electric Motors”, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2258, “Inspecting and Cleaning Subsurface Drain Systems”, 1975 July (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2260, “Catfish Farming”, 1975 November (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2264, “Lamb: Slaughtering, Cutting, Preserving, and Cooking on the Farm”, 1977 August (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - “Farmers’ Bulletin”, #2266, “Solar Heating for Milking Parlors”, 1977 September (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Announcements, 1976-1978 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Clippings and Printed Materials, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Clippings, Legislative Reports, and Printed Materials, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Community Programs, List, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence and Clippings, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Engineers, Clippings and Correspondence, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Falls County, Scrapbook, 1966-1973 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Pamphlets and Programs, 1950-1951 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Pamphlets, 1968-1972 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases and Reports, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases and Reports, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Press Releases and Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Report, “Acts of Congress Administered by or Affecting the Farmers Home Administration”, 1971 May (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Report to Governor Steve McNichols, 1957 July 1 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Reports, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Rural Community Projects, Correspondence and Financial Report, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Farmers Home Administration, Rural Development, Correspondence and Reports, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Federal Crop Insurance, Correspondence, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Federal Crop Insurance, Correspondence and Statement, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Federal Crop Insurance, Report, 1976 March (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Act, Reports and Statements, 1972-1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Corporation, Annual Report, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Corporation, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Federal Crop Insurance Corporation, Pamphlet, “Federal All-Risk Crop InsuranceELWhy”, 1964 October (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Federal Grain Inspection Service, Statement, Donald E. Wilkinson, 1977 January 31 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Food Distribution Office, Temple, Texas, Reports, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - “Foreign Agricultural Trade”, Newsletters, 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Foreign Agriculture, Clippings and Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Agriculture, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Agriculture Service, Pamphlet and Proposal, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Forest Service, “Pusch Ridge Wilderness Management Plan”, Draft, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Glass Containers for Peanut Butter, Correspondence and Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Great Plains Conservation Program, Maps, 1957-1959 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Guayule, Articles and Report, 1966-1970 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Guayule, Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Handbook, Agricultural Charts, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #8, “Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables”, 1976 May (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #10, “Home Freezing of Fruits and Vegetables”, 1976 September (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #17, “Food Guide for Older Folks”, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #56, “How to Make Jellies, Jams, and Preserves at Home”, 1977 June (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #61, “Lawn Diseases: How to Control Them”, 1977 October (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #62, “Removing Stains from Fabrics”, 1977 May (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #64, “Subterranean Termites: Their Prevention and Control in Buildings”, 1977 May (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #65, “Growing Chrysanthemums in the Home Garden”, 1976 September (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #66, “Growing Iris in the Home Garden”, 1975 December (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #67, “Insects and Related Pests of House Plants”, 1977 October (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #68, “How to Prevent and Remove Mildew: Home Methods”, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #69 Home Care of Purchased Frozen Foods”, 1975 May (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #71, “Growing Azaleas and Rhododendrons”, 1976 September (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #72, “Nutritive Value of Foods”, 1977 April (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #73, “Wood Decay in Houses: How to Prevent and Control It”, 1977 August (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #74, “Food and Your Weight”, 1977 November (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #75, “The European Earwig: How to Control It Around the Home”, 1977 April (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #77, “Family Food Stockpile for Survival”, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #78, “Storing Perishable Foods in the Home”, 1976 April (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #80, “Home Propagation of Ornamental Trees and Shrubs”, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #81, “Maple Diseases and Their Control: A Guide for Homeowners”, 1976 September (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #82, “Selecting and Growing House Plants”, 1976 September (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #83, “Pruning Shade Trees and Repairing Their Injuries”, 1976 May (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #86, “Growing Camellias”, 1977 July (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #88, “Growing the Flowering Dogwood”, 1977 November (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #89, “Selecting Fertilizers for Lawns and Gardens”, 1973 February (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #89, “Selecting Fertilizers for Lawns and Gardens”, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #90, “Conserving the Nutritive Values in Foods”, 1977 November (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #91, “Growing Flowering Annuals”, 1975 October (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #93, “Freezing Meat and Fish in the Home”, 1977 May (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #94, “Family Food Budgeting”, 1976 November (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #96, “Controlling Household Pests”, 1977 June (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #98, “A Guide to Budgeting for the Young Couple”, 1977 July (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #102, “Iron Deficiency in Plants: How to Control It in Yards and Gardens”, 1976 February (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #103, “Eggs in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1973 October (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #104, “Protecting Shade Trees During Home Construction”, 1975 September (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #105, “Vegetables in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1975 January (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #106, “Home Canning of Meat and Poultry”, 1975 February (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #108, “A Guide to Budgeting for the Family”, 1976 March (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #112, “Cheese in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1977 September (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #114, “Growing Flowering Perennials”, 1976 February (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #117, “Trees for Shade and Beauty”, 1976 April (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #118, “Beef and Veal in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1978 January (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #119, “Storing Vegetables and Fruits in Basements, Cellars, Outbuildings, and Pits”, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #120, “Growing Boxwoods”, 1976 January (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #121, “Controlling Fleas”, 1976 June (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #122, “Controlling Wasps”, 1978 February (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #124, “Lamb in Family Meals”, 1977 May (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #125, “Fruits in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1975 February (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #127, “Milk in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1974 December (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #129, “Making Cottage Cheese at Home”, 1975 December (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #130, “Growing Hollies”, 1977 February (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #131, “Growing Dahlias”, 1977 October (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #136, “Spring Flowering Bulbs”, 1977 September (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #137, “Controlling Chiggers”, 1976 April (Box 67, Folder 54)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #141, “How to Buy Fresh Fruits”, 1977 August (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #143, “How to Buy Fresh Vegetables”, 1967 December (Box 67, Folder 56)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #144, “How to Buy Eggs”, 1975 October (Box 67, Folder 57)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #147, “Baking for People with Food Allergies”, 1975 May (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #149, “Growing Pansies”, 1977 July (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #151, “Summer Flowering Bulbs”, 1971 February (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #152, “Growing Gardenias”, 1977 October (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #154, “Growing the Bradford Ornamental Pear”, 1971 June (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #157, “How to Buy Poultry”, 1977 June (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #158, “Beekeeping for Beginners”, 1975 August (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #159, “Controlling the Japanese Beetle”, 1976 December (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #160, “Pork in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1977 July (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #161, “Apples in Appealing Ways”, 1977 November (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #162, “Keeping Food Safe to Eat: A Guide for Homemakers”, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #163, “Minigardens for Vegetables”, 1974 May (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #165, “Pruning Ornamental Shrubs and Vines”, 1975 October (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #166, “How to Buy Meat for Your Freezer”, 1976 October (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #167, “How to Buy Canned and Frozen Vegetables”, 1975 January (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #168, “House Construction: How to Reduce Costs”, 1977 April (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #169, “How to Buy Lawn Seed”, 1969 August (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #175, “Growing Ground Covers”, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #176, “Nuts in Family Meals: A Guide for Consumers”, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #178, “Controlling the Eastern Tent Caterpillar”, 1973 April (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #179, “Gardening on the Contour”, 1976 March (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #180, “Growing Tomatoes in the Home Garden”, 1978 May (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #181, “Shrubs, Vines, and Trees for Summer Color”, 1977 March (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #182, “Selecting and Financing a Home”, 1977 September (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #186, “Breads, Cakes, and Pies in Family Meals”, 1976 June (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #188, “Growing Ornamentals in Urban Gardens”, 1977 May (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #189, “How to Buy a Christmas Tree”, 1971 October (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #191, How to Buy Canned and Frozen Fruits”, 1977 July (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #192, “Transplanting Ornamental Trees and Shrubs”, 1977 June (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #193, “How to Buy Cheese”, 1977 May (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #195, “How to Buy Lamb”, 1971 August (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #196, “How to Use USDA Grades in Buying Food”, 1977 March (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #198, “How to Buy Potatoes”, 1972 February (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #199, “Growing Lilacs”, 1977 October (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #200, “Be Safe from Insects in Recreation Areas”, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #201, “How to Buy Dairy Products”, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #202, “Growing Vegetables in the Home Garden”, 1978 May (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #203, “Wood Siding: Installing, Finishing, Maintaining”, 1975 July (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #204, “Growing Apricots for Home Use”, 1977 May (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #205, “Selecting and Growing Shade Trees”, 1978 May (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #206, “Growing Bonsai”, 1977 February (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #207, “Thornless Blackberries for the Home Garden”, 1975 February (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #208, “Soybeans in Family Meals”, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #209, “Food for the Family — A Cost Saving Plan”, 1976 May (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #210, “Drainage Around Your Home”, 1975 September (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #211, “Control of Insects on Deciduous Fruits and Tree Nuts in the Home Orchard — Without Insecticides”, 1975 July (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #212, “Renovate an Old House?”, 1976 March (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #214, “Insects on Trees and Shrubs Around the Home”, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #215, “Selections from Aunt Sammy’s Radio Recipes and USDA Favorites”, 1976 August (Box 68, Folder 49)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #216, “Food is More than Just Something to Eat”, 1976 July (Box 68, Folder 50)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #217, “Drying Foods at Home”, 1977 January (Box 68, Folder 51)
    - “Home and Garden Bulletin”, #223, “Defoliation by the Gypsy Moth: How It Hurts Your Tree”, 1978 January (Box 68, Folder 52)
    - Holly Sugar Corporation, Hereford, Texas, Correspondence and Essay, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 53)
    - Irrigation Rights, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 54)
    - Jobs Development Incentive Act of 1967, Summary, 1967 April (Box 68, Folder 55)
    - Leaflet #172, “Why Fruit Trees Fail to Bear”, 1976 April (Box 68, Folder 56)
    - Leaflet #187, “Blight of Pears, Apples and Quinces”, 1976 June (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Leaflet #309, “Preventing Greenbug Outbreaks”, 1977 August (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Leaflet #321, “What to Do When Your Home Freezer Stops”, 1972 September (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Leaflet #335, “Farming Terraced Land”, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Leaflet #346, “GrassELthe Rancher’s Crop”, 1972 June (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Leaflet #360, “Growing Table Beets”, 1976 August (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Leaflet #382, “The Fowl Tick: How to Control It”, 1974 February (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Leaflet #390, “The House Fly: How to Control It”, 1975 November (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Leaflet #393, “Cecal Coccidiosis of Chickens: How to Control It”, 1974 February (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Leaflet #407, “Dwarf Fruit Trees: Selection and Care”, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Leaflet #424, “Food for Fitness: A Daily Food Guide”, 1977 September (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Leaflet #428, “Trichinosis”, 1968 September (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Leaflet #444, “The Narcissus Bulb Fly: How to Prevent Its Damage in Home Gardens”, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Leaflet #445, “Electric Healing of Hotbeds”, 1975 December (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Leaflet #450, “Horse Bots: How to Control Them”, 1976 February (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Leaflet #452, “Replenishing Underground Water Supplies on the Farm”, 1976 April (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Leaflet #453, “How to Control Bed Bugs”, 1976 April (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Leaflet #458, “Autumn Olive: For Wildlife and Other Conservation Uses”, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Leaflet #476, “Sprinkler Irrigation”, 1977 October (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Leaflet #477, “Grass Waterways in Soil Conservation”, 1977 April (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Leaflet #487, “Planting Black Walnut for Timber”, 1976 January (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Leaflet #492, “The Common Liver Fluke in Sheep”, 1975 August (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Leaflet #500, “Milky Disease for Control of Japanese Beetle Grubs”, 1973 March (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Leaflet #501, “The Old House Borer”, 1976 September (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Leaflet #502, “Spider Mites on Cotton: How to Control Them”, 1968 November (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Leaflet #505, “Tuberculosis in Livestock”, 1962 March (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Leaflet #508, “Bridge Grafting and Inarching Damaged Fruit Trees”, 1977 November (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Leaflet #510, “Zoning for Rural Areas”, 1976 September (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Leaflet #513, “The Chip-Bud Method of Propagating Vinifera Grape Varieties on Rootstocks”, 1976 July (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Leaflet #517, “Russian-Olive for Wildlife and Other Conservation Uses”, 1976 January (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Leaflet #519, “Raising Guinea Fowl”, 1976 April (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Leaflet #523, “Canada Thistle and Its Control”, 1977 January (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Leaflet #525, “Growing Black Walnuts for Home Use”, 1974 February (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Leaflet #530, “Shade and Water for the Honey Bee Colony”, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Leaflet #531, “Growing Red Clover”, 1973 September (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Leaflet #532, “How to Plan a Shooting Field in the Northeast and Corn Belt”, 1973 March (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - Leaflet #535, “Building with Adobe and Stabilized-Earth Blocks”, 1977 January (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - Leaflet #546, “Fescue Foot in Cattle: What to Do About It”, 1971 October (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - Leaflet #548, “Controlling the Mexican Bean Beetle”, 1977 May (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - Leaflet #549, “Using Honey Bees to Pollinate Crops”, 1977 May (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - Leaflet #552, “Trout Farming: Could Trout Farming be Profitable for You?”, 1975 January (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Leaflet #553, “Controlling Insects in Farm-Stored Grain”, 1971 May (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Leaflet #554, “Mulch Tillage in Modern Farming”, 1977 January (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Leaflet #555, “Rhubarb Production”, 1976 October (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Leaflet #556, “Controlling the Brown Recluse Spider”, 1973 November (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - Leaflet #557, “Maintaining Subsurface Drains”, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - Leaflet #560, “Bark Mulch: Natural Artistry Around Your House”, 1975 July (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - Leaflet #562, “Maintaining Watercourses”, 1975 November (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - Leaflet #563, “Pesticides and Honey Bees”, 1977 November (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - Leaflet #565, “Constructing an Effective Anticoyote Electric Fence”, 1978 January (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - Legal Complaint, “National Corn Growers Association, Incorporated, and Corn Refiners Association, Incorporated v. Robert Bergland et. al.”, 1977 October (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - Legal Documents, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - Legal Documents, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 53)
    - Legislative Materials, 1966 February-March (Box 69, Folder 54)
    - Legislative Materials, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 55)
    - List of Beer and Wine Establishments, Falls, McLennan, and Milam Counties, undated (Box 69, Folder 56)
    - Map, “Sales Control Map of the Southeast”, 1966 (Box 149 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Marketing, Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1958-1961 (Box 69, Folder 57)
    - Marketing and Consumer Services, Poultry and Egg Division, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1967-1974 (Box 69, Folder 58)